bestbrandsworldwide.com 2016-11-23

# Privacy Policy

We collect information from you when you register on our site. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL -  <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/>

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

; To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [online privacy policy](http://www.bestbrandsworldwide.com/content/privacy-policy).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 3/23/2012

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

privacy@bestbrandsworldwide.com
